Zakaria Wahyu Web Developer



ABOUT



Hallo, I'm Zakaria Wahyu Nur Utomo. I was born June 25th 1999 at Klaten, Central Java, Indonesia. As informatic engineering associate degree students of Telkom University, I have a lot of experience on web and android programming. My curiousity is good when finish my project web based. I'm creative person that like to create something new and able to solving some problem. I'm hard worker, able to teamwork, good communication, and always have a goals in every decision.



- 082 329 027 297
- zakarianur6@gmail.com
- linkedin.com/in/zakariawahyu
- Bandung, West Java, Indonesia

PORTFOLIO

- github.com/zakariawahyu
- zakariawahyu.github.io

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer Internship

2020

Augmented Reality Enginer Internship

Web Programming Practicum Assistant

2018 - 2020

Head of Team

2018 - 2019

HUMAN RESOURCE TELKOM UNIVERSITY

I'm became web developer to help Directorate of Human Resource Telkom University for develop staffing structural position application that make it easier for HR to determine any vacant position. I use feamework laravel in building this

PT. INOVASI SEMESTA ILMU

I had an opportunity to internship at PT. Inovasi Semesta Ilmu Bandung Company to build an application VR and AR based. That application used to promote tourism in Bandung more easier. I used Unity 3D to build this application and Samsung Gear 360 to take the VR.

TELKOM APPLIED SCIENCES SCHOOL

I'm an assistant practicum at many Telkom University Applied Sciences Schools study programs. I have a lot of experience for example help lecturers to practicum, recapitulation of values practicum, and create modules for practice html, css, php, javascript and database every week for students.

PERFECTO 2.0

PERFECTO (PaMTKla Exhibition Roadshow and Fun Education Tryout) is a commite under the Directorate of Admission Telkom University which has a goals to hold roadshow activities and try out to promote and communicate about information of Telkom University to public.

BASICS SKILLS

HTML **REACT JS** PHP LARAVEL / CI JAVA

EDUCATION

SMA N 1 **KARANGANOM**

2014 - 2017

Telkom University

2017 - 2020

Natural Sciences

I was graduated at 2017. When I was SHS student, I had a lot of leadership experience because I joined National Flag Hoisting Troop

Informatics Engineering Associate Degree

During 3 years of college I have a lot of experience in web programming, android programming, iot, and multimedia. But I am more focused to explore web programming

SOFTWARE SKILLS

PHOTOSHOP PREMIERE PRO ILLUSTRATOR ADOBE XD UNITY 3D ANDROID STUDIO

CERTIFICATE

Android Beginer

2020 - 2022

Android

Expert 2020- 2022

Dicoding Indonesia

Learn basic android programming that learns how to create relative layouts, recycler view, activity and intent

Dicoding Indonesia

Learn android fundamentals that learn how to make fragment, action bar, tab layout, navigation, services, broadcast receiver, alarm manager, job scheduler, viewmodel, widget, notification, firebase and webview